你就没准备睡觉吗
Are you ever coming to bed?
我还是要说我是个素食主义者
I still say I'm a vegetarian.
好吧  你还能说你是宇航员呢
Well, you can say that you're an astronaut,
但这是异想天开
but that doesn't make it true.
鲑鱼肉不是素食  弗兰琪
A salmon is not a vegetable, Frankie.
好吧  显然 十分之八的留言同意你的说法
Well, apparently, eight out of ten commenters agree with you.
但不认同你说的这部分
Except for the part where you said,
"我信故我信"
"I believe what I want to believe."
他们觉得这句话有争议
That they found a little judgmental.
你把我们的争吵内容写进博客了吗
You blogged our argument?
我和你说过不要把我写进博客
I asked you to quit talking about me.
我不想让一堆陌生人
I don't want a bunch of people that I don't know
知道原本是我们两个人之间的私事
hearing stuff that's meant to be between me and you.
我写的是我的生活
I write about my life.
而你是其中重要的一部分
And you're a big part of that.
很好  我想成为你生活中的一部分
That's great. I want to be a big part of your life.
但不是他们的
But I don't want to be a big part of their lives.
别写了  全部清除  删掉它
Take it down, erase it, delete it.
让它们全部消失
Make it go away.
老兄  现在可是凌晨两点
Come on, man. It's 2:00 in the morning.
这墙简直是纸片做的
These walls are made out of tissue paper.
三个小时后我就得起床去爱迪生家做个布线工作
I gotta be up in three hours to do a wiring job in Edison's.
很抱歉  我们会尽量小点声
I'm sorry. We'll try to hold it down.
抱歉
Sorry.
弗兰琪  你怎么了
Frankie, what happened?
不  不不是你想的那样  肯定是出了什么问题
No. No. That's not what you think. Something's wrong.
我们需要一辆警车 哈福希尔152号
We need a police car at 152 Haverhill.
你们两个说什么呢
Whoa, what are you two talking about?
天呐
Oh, my god.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
好像是从牙床上流出来的
I think it's coming from my gums.
今晚你做些什么
What are you doing tonight?
打手枪
Masturbating.
我本想邀请你一起但别人已经开始传我们的流言了
I'd invite you, but people are already talking.
真可悲
It's pathetic.
你的晚间娱乐不是A片就是探索频道
You divide your nights between porn and the discovery channel.
行了  那是病人送我的礼物
Okay, that was a gift from a patient,
而且碰巧是项不错的运动
and it happens to be great exercise.
我说  这年头谁还会去租A片呢
I mean, who rents porn anymore?
你不能在网上看吗
Can't you get this stuff on the internet?
可以
You can.
但你看不到第二张碟的导演解说
But you can't get disc two with the director's commentary.
今晚和我出去吧
Come out with me tonight.
我要去参加多人速配
I'm going speed dating.
你要去嗑药派对吗
You mean you're dating on meth?
-算我一个  -你得出去认识些新朋友
- Count me in. - You need to meet somebody.
这种方法可以一次认识20个
This way, you meet 20 somebodies.
通过对普鲁斯特[法国小说家]的五分钟讨论
Over a five-minute discussion of proust?
多人速配就是人肉市场
Speed dating's a meat market.
没错  成打的女人在等着被吊
Yeah, dozens of women just waiting to be hit on.
你压在美好归宿的赔率
Your odds of a happy ending are nearly as good
和你在家看A片的一样多
as staying home and watching porn.
今天你有什么工作安排吗
You plan on doing any work today?
我想我会在下午做一点点医生工作
I thought I might do a little light doctoring in the afternoon.
28岁女性突然产生不知原因的凝血障碍
28-year-old female sudden unexplained coagulopathy.
可能是先天性血小板减少症
Could be congenital thrombocytopenia.
血小板看起来正常
Platelets look normal.
病人是自由职业摄影师
Patient makes money doing freelance photography.
摄影中有些过程产生有毒气体
Some photographic processes produce toxic gases.
她写博客
She's a blogger.
我看她拍的都是数码照片
I can't see her photos being anything but digital.
她博客都写什么内容
What does she blog?
政治看法  母夜叉论  烹饪心得吗
Politics? Dominatrix? Cooking?
因为我需要食谱
'Cause I need recipes.
是私人日记
It's a personal journal.
我理解不了把个人生活发表在网上的人
I don't get putting your whole life online.
也没那么夸张
It's not that crazy.
隐私可以说是近代产物
Privacy's basically a modern invention.
曾经的城镇小得令人不可能保住任何秘密
Towns used to be too small for anybody to keep any secrets.
如果不是血小板的原因而是某种胶粘物把它们凝结的呢
What if it's not the platelets, but the glue that holds 'em together?
不
No.
凝血酶和血管性血友病因子正常
Thrombin and von willebrand factor are normal.
而相互之间太过了解
And knowing too much about each other
正是人们离开小城镇搬进大城市的原因
is exactly why people leave small towns and move to the city.
而很多人留在小城镇
And a lot of people choose to stay
是因为完全无隐私
because, in return for zero privacy,
能换来社交圈子和联系纽带的回报
you get community, connection.
又红又长的纽带  可以用来绑外套
Big red as for our tunics.
联系纽带是给机场带来盈利的
Connections are for airports.
对普通人来说  我们有300个有线频道
For people, we have over 300 cable channels.
也许她拍数码照片
Her photos may be digital
但不意味着她没有暴露在其他毒素里
doesn't mean she couldn't have been exposed to some other toxin.
我们应该检查一下她的寓所
We should search the apartment.
点  点  点芝麻  13和小小陶去
Eeny, Meeny, Miny, thirteen and tiny.
这个锁上了
This one's locked.
你这么亲近社会真令我惊讶
I'm surprised you took the pro-community position.
我有不少朋友  我喜欢与人交往
I have friends. I like people.
你也喜欢秘密
You also like secrets.
你否定它
You deny it,
就进一步证明了我的观点
it sort of proves my point.
我们走进自己的圈套时
When we're left to our own devices,
总会做出糟糕的选择
we make lousy choices.
别管它
Ignore it.
我听见你们在里面了
I can hear you in there.
开门  不然我叫警察了
Open the door, or I'm calling the cops.
我们在4层  但外面墙上有个有个防火梯
We're four stories up, but there's a fire escape on the other wall.
壁架也许足够宽能容纳我们
The ledge might be wide enough.
我们是医生  没有偷任何东西
We're doctors. We aren't stealing anything.
我们在收集样品
We're collecting samples.
-你是谁  -邻居
- Who are you? - The neighbor.
他们同意你们进入还...
Did they say that you could come in here and...
是的  你了解弗兰琪和泰勒吗
Yup. What do you know about Frankie and Taylor?
不是很清楚
Not much.
男的经常在外工作
The guy works a lot.
我有时遇见弗兰琪
I see Frankie around.
我们一周争论几次
We argue a few times a week,
然后各回各家
and then we go back about our business.
你们争论些什么
What do you argue about?
弗兰琪强烈要求
Frankie's got some strong opinions.
把垃圾回收分类细化
wants to recycle every molecule of trash.
你站在反对垃圾回收那边
You take the anti-recycling position?
垃圾堆肥会招来临近的每一只老鼠
Trash piling up for composting's attracting every rat in the neighborhood.
我不得不投放鼠药
I had to put down poison.
那是她的私人抽屉  你要干什么
It's her private drawer. What are you doing over there?
她说她没有任何秘密
She said she doesn't have any secrets.
我得到她的同意了
I'm taking her at her word.
弗兰琪有没有可能接触到鼠药
Is there any chance Frankie touched the rat poison?
接触吗  她曾经在大厅
Touched it? She grabbed a chunk of it
从一只雪纳瑞猎犬嘴里
right out of the mouth of the schnauzer
拽出过一大块
From down the hall.
现在每次我投药  她都把它们扔掉
Now every time I put the stuff down, she picks it back up.
你还带来个情侣吗
You brought a date?
威尔森觉得这是个好主意
Wilson seemed to think it was a good idea.
你需要重回池子
You need to dive back into the pool.
非要在我们的池子里游吗
And he has to swim in ours?
去酒吧的时候要带个丑朋友相衬
You go to a bar, you bring your ugly friends.
这又不是选美比赛
It's not a beauty pageant.
生活就是选美比赛
Life is a beauty pageant.
小姑娘都梦想着亲吻青蛙后变成你这样的
Little girls who kiss frogs expect them to turn into you.
得了  我没那么好看
Oh, come on. I'm not that good-looking.
错了  你有
Yeah, you are.
你是挺好看的
You kind of are.
所以你们把我至今获得青睐的原因
So you attribute every relationship
都归结到我的颧骨高度上吗[帅气脸庞]
I've ever had to the height of my cheekbones?
并不是从头至尾的恋情
Not the whole relationship.
-只是开头  -剩下的是你头发的作用
- Just the beginning. - The rest is your hair.
太可笑了
This is ridiculous.
女人并不像我们一样只会被外表迷惑
Women aren't as distracted by appearances as we are.
他们看得更深
They look deeper.
想赌一把吗
You wanna bet?
你不可以告诉别人你是名医生
You can't tell anyone you're a doctor.
只能说你失业中
You're unemployed.
你还要表现得有点迟钝
You're also a little slow,
误解她们说的所有事情
Misunderstanding everything they say.
改改口音
And lose the accent.
赌一百块  赌你就算这样还是能带着一打名字离开这里
A hundred bucks says you still walk out of here with a dozen names.
女士们  先生们  游戏马上就开始了
Ladies and gentlemen, the fun is about to start.
我敲锣时  每个人就坐到指定的座位上
When I strike this gong, each man should sit at the table you've been assigned.
当我再敲时  约会就结束了
When I strike it again, date's over,
开始吧
Move on.
我是一个脑肿瘤学专家
I'm an oncologist.
我的婶婶和奶奶  她们都死于乳腺癌
Oh, my aunt and my grandma, they both died From breast cancer.
你想  想谈谈吗
Do--do you wanna talk about it?
我是一名诊断专家
I'm a diagnostician.
我找出人们的毛病  再治好它
I find out what's wrong with people, and I fix it.
医生不都干这个吗
Don't all doctors do that?
是的  但他们不能像我一样跳舞
Yeah, but they can't dance like I can.
我爱打电玩
I play video games.
专业的吗
Oh. Professionally?
我希望如此  哥们
I wish, bro.
经过六个月的化疗  我们以为他脱离了险境
After six months of chemo, we thought he was out of the woods.
-我不想要孩子  -明白
- I don't want kids. - Check.
我想从C罩杯变成D罩杯
I'm thinking about going from a "C" to a "D."
明白乘以四
Quadruple check.
我很崇拜上帝
And I'm on fire for the lord.
我是个巧克力销售商
I'm a chocolatier.
我看你屁股就知道了
I could tell by your hips.
是吧  我觉得我还能减掉几磅重
Yeah, I guess I could afford to lose a few pounds.
我不认识死于癌症的人
I don't think I know anybody who died of cancer.
感谢上帝
Thank god.
为你好  我是指
For you, I mean.
很明显
Obviously.
除了我的猫
Except my cat.
她几个月前去世了
She died a few months ago.
我讨厌这些
I hate these things.
什么  你被顶在枪口上吗
What, are you here at gunpoint?
你需要我打911吗
You need me to call 911?
朋友把我硬拉过来的
Friend dragged me.
她总想补救我的生活
She keeps trying to fix my life.
不可否认  可能有点用  只是
Which, admittedly, could use it, but...
还是很烦人
Still annoying.
你喜欢字谜
You like puzzles.
我希望我的工作能让自己成天到晚都猜字谜
I hoped my job would let me play with puzzles all day long,
不过事实不如人愿
But it didn't work out that way.
警局侦探
Police detective.
结果是罪犯都像傻子
Turns out criminals are idiots.
如果他们不准备动脑筋挑战你的话
If they're not gonna bother to challenge you,
有什么意思呢
What's the point?
有没有火警让供我们拉响呢
Is there a fire alarm we could pull?
也许能从这离开
Maybe get out of here.
除了
Except...
也许你太工于心计了
Maybe you're just too swoft.
-能再说一遍吗  -工于心计
- Beg your pardon. - Swoft.
这是你的字谜答案之一
It's one of your crossword answers.
我猜意思是谎言操纵者
I believe it means lying manipulator
总是说别人想听的话
Who tells men anything they want to hear.
你带了一个道具充当谈话的触发点
You brought a prop as a conversation starter.
把报纸叠起来  看上去你正在读
Folded the paper to make it look read,
填一些答案  但是你并不想
Filled in some answers, but you couldn't be bothered
真的攻克它们  所以你只是随便填了些数字
To work at it, so you just put in random letters.
你有做撒谎者的天赋
You have some natural talent as a liar,
不过想要通关  你还不够格
But not enough brains to see it through.
我大胆断言你并不是警察
I'm gonna assume you're not a cop.
五分钟到了吗
Are the five minutes up?
这些女士愿意你打电话给她们
These women would welcome a call from you.
这些女士愿意你打电话
And these women would welcome a call from you.
天啊
My.
有访客总是好的
It's nice to have visitors.
我在更新我的博客
I'm updating my blog.
我在阅读它
And I'm reading it.
你们知道你们俩是在同一件屋子吧
You realize you're in the same room?
不好意思
Sorry.
我已经考虑过你说的了
So I've been thinking about what you said.
我确定每次扔完老鼠药都洗过手
And I'm sure I washed my hands after I threw out the rat poison.
很显然  你一段时间内
Apparently you did it multiple times
要重复很多次
Over a course of days.
所以不能下定论
Can't be too certain.
你一定福曼医生了
You must be Dr. Foreman.
得回去工作了
Got to get back to work.
好的  放轻松点
Okay. Take it easy.
怎么了
What?
她读过我的博客
She reads my blog.
个人觉得  你没有那么高傲
Personally, I don't think you're condescending at all.
我不是这么写的
That's not what I wrote.
当你问我要病史的时候
When you were taking my history,
我告诉你六个月前  我参加了激流勇进
I told you I went whitewater rafting six months ago,
你说  这看起来无关吧
And you said, "It was unlikely to be related."
我只是在提供信息
I was just giving information.
别遮掩了  你确实语气有点差
Let's face it. You got a little snarky.
你不能书写语调吧
You can't convey a tone of voice in writing.
我只写了你所说的
I just put what you said.
如果你不想让人们觉得你傲慢
If you don't want people To think you're condescending,
也许你就不应该讲些傲慢的事情
Maybe you shouldn't say condescending things.
可以等一下再说吗  我想去厕所
Can this wait a second? 'cause I have to pee.
我觉得人们之所以行为不端
You know, I think people behave badly
是因为我们的言行没有被记录下来
Because there are no records Of what we say or do.
没有人再相信上帝正注视着我们
And nobody believes anymore that God's watching.
上帝虽然没有  但是我有
Well, God's not, but I am.
任何事都被记录下来
Everything is on the record,
包括我做过的每件事
Including everything I do.
我觉得
I don't think
我的尿液不应该是泥土色吧
My pee is supposed to be mud-colored.
我们关于鼠毒诊断是错的
We were wrong about the rat poison.
凝血病加肾脏问题等于什么
Coagulopathy plus kidney equals what?
溶血尿毒综合症
Hemolytic uremic syndrome.
肌氨酸酐水平正常  她的胆固醇指数升高了
Normal creatinine levels. She has elevated cholesterol.
喂  威尔森
Hey, Wilson!
找不到我的黄色录像带了
Can't find my pornos.
你没有试试悬赏吗
Have you tried offering a reward?
高雪氏疾病
Gaucher's disease.
那会影响她合成维他命K的能力
It would affect her ability to synthesize vitamin k.
她是半素食主义者
She's on a semi-vegetarian diet.
意味着她获得了足量的维他命K
Means she gets plenty of vitamin k.
更像是萧格伦综合症
Sjogren's is more likely.
我以为你打扫的时候把它们收起来了
I assume you moved them while you were dusting.
我检查了抽屉  窗台
I checked the drawers, windowsill,
还有你房间里的dvd播放器
Dvd player in your room.
沉默者多数总是性压抑的一群
The quiet ones are always deeply repressed.
我把它们还了
I returned them to the store.
她前几天吃了一顿鱼宴
She had a fish dinner a couple of nights ago.
可能是哈罗病引起的狂犬病毒
Could be Haff disease causing rhabdo.
什么  你为什么要还回去呢
What? Why did you return them to the store?
又不麻烦
It's no trouble.
我顺便要在旁边的商店取干洗的衣服
I had to stop next-door for my dry cleaning anyway.
萧格伦不会抑制凝固酶
Sjogren's wouldn't inhibit the clotting enzymes,
渗透到了肾脏  一切真相大白
Infiltrate the kidneys-- explains everything.
哈罗病也可以
So does Haff disease.
我不是在谢谢你  我在问你为什么
I'm not thanking you. I'm asking you why.
因为如果我昨晚真的碰巧带了一个女人回家
Because if I did happen to bring a woman home last night,
我希望那里是黄色禁区
I wanted it to be a porn-free zone.
你应该知道装进袜柜里的东西不一定非要是袜子吧
You do realize things don't have to be socks To go into a sock drawer.
对不起
I'm sorry.
非常  非常抱歉
Horribly, horribly sorry.
我以为你  已经全部看完了
I thought you'd... watched them all.
你彻底毁掉了我的上午
You completely ruined my morning.
我不得不翻你的家庭旧照
I had to pull out your old family photos.
你妈妈很性感
Your mom was pretty hot.
哈罗病最符合时间序列
Haff disease fits the timing best.
给她使用盐溶液和甘露醇
Start her on saline and mannitol.
你读了你病人的博客吗
You reading your patient's blog?
没有
Nope.
你应该读
You should.
也许能发现一些线索
Could be some clues.
线索太多  就像做全身扫描一样
Too many. Be like doing a whole body scan.
会指出8个错误的方向
Send us up eight blind alleys.
因此我让奇斯看
That's why chase is doing it.
她提到你了
She mentions you.
她还没见过我
She's never met me.
你是看不见的精灵
You're an unseen presence,
像奥兹国的巫师一样[出自绿野仙踪]
Like the wizard of OZ.
他以前是个骗子
He was a fraud.
她为什么不能跟着keyser soze走呢[超强黑社会老大]
She couldn't have gone with keyser soze?
说到电影的不合理
Speaking of movies that don't make any sense,
我去了租赁店  把色情片拿了回来
I stopped at the rental store to get those pornos back.
我告诉店员我很感谢
I told the guy at the counter I was so grateful
你帮我还了片子  不过我想要回来
That you'd returned them, but I wanted them.
你猜怎么样
Guess what.
你只还了两部
You only returned two.
把第三部弄掉了
You lost the third.
你真好心帮我付了钱
It's decent of you to pay for it,
没有算在我的账上
Not let them put it on my bill.
其实...
You know...
我可以解释是怎么回事
I can explain what happened.
我知道你可以
I'm sure you could.
不过比起听你说谎
But rather than listen to your lies,
我觉得开车到镇的那头去借同样的版本
I thought it'd be more fun to drive all over town
会更有意思
And get another copy.
它现在在你手里吗
You have-- you have it here?
噢  天呢
Oh, god.
Oh, god!
好吧  第一
Okay, first,
那不是我
That's not me.
那不是  大部分都不是
It's not-- mostly not--
我当时在读大学
I was in college.
我不是...我室友当时辅修
I don't...my roommate was minoring
摄像课程
In film.
你是否得了换气过度
Are you hyperventilating?
记住  堵住嘴巴和一只鼻孔可以缓解
Remember that covering your mouth and one nostril can help.
他为了某门课有成绩必须交这个他当时十分绝望
He had to get this in for some grade, And he was desperate.
我去做这个的唯一原因是我以为别人永远也不会看到
And the only reason I did it was because no one would ever see it.
谁知道他会真的变成导演
Who knew he'd become an actual director?
他不是个导演
He's not a director.
他是艺术家
He's an artist.
他驾驭光影...和胸部的能力
The way he plays with light and darkness and...boobs.
这个不是我
That's not me.
你是什么
What are you?
你为什么抱着我
Where are you taking me?
千万别怕
Be not afraid.
森林女神已经教过我如何取悦女人了
The forest nymphs have taught me how to please a woman.
这不是我
That's not me.
这不是...你可以清楚看到这不是我
That's not...I mean, you can see it's not me.
他加了一段
He added extra scenes
所以他能以色情片发行
So he could release it as a porno.
千万别怕  威尔森
Be not afraid, wilson.
你是为艺术献身的
You took risks for your art.
噢
Oh, boy.
没人...嗨  看着我
No one...hey, look at me.
永远不能让别人看到这个
No one can know about this.
从这一刻开始  我会守口如瓶的
From this moment on, my lips are sealed.
-对不起  -没事
- Sorry. - It's okay.
千万别怕
Be not afraid.
发现什么吗
Find anything?
没发现相关的
Relevant? No.
倒是有有意思的
Interesting. I guess.
她什么都和别人分享
There's nothing that she doesn't share.
"愤怒中的性生活被过高评价了"
"Angry sex is overrated.
"他怎会期望我在对他如此生气时有性欲呢"
"How can he expect me to be aroused when I'm so pissed at him?"
揭露这样的真相也许能帮她获得一个新肾脏
Revelations like that might just earn her a new kidney.
她在博客上写她肾衰竭后的一小时
An hour after she blogged about her kidney failure,
医院就会接到新加坡打来的电话
The hospital got a call from Singapore.
弗兰琪的某个读者询问如何捐赠肾脏的事
One of Frankie's readers asking how hard it would be to donate.
我到底有多帅
How good-looking am I?
我不是问你  你是否被我吸引
I'm not asking if you're attracted to me.
我在寻求一个客观的答案
I'm looking for an objective answer.
这样啊  那倒真是个合适的问题啊
Oh, okay, then it's an appropriate question.
昨晚  我表现地像个傻瓜
Last night, I acted like a complete tosser
为向豪斯证明  女人不因为长相 和我约会
To prove to house that women don't go out with me for my looks.
我损失了100美金
Cost me a hundred bucks
让我开始不了解自己
And my definition of myself.
还有女人们和男人约会吧
And women. So date men.
他们一点也不肤浅
They're not shallow at all.
一切都是有关肉体
Everything's physical.
是  人类是肉体的动物
Yes. We are physical beings.
或多或少
Some more than others.
请不要以一个晚上来定义我的性别
Please don't define my entire gender based on one night.
不  会不会她的问题是一个生理反应
No, what if the patient's problem is a physical reaction,
而不是情感上的
Not an emotional one?
她缺乏性欲是否与他们的争吵毫无关系呢
What if her lack of arousal Had nothing to do with their fight?
干燥综合征会抑制她阴道液体的分泌
Sjogren's would inhibit her normal secretions.
抱歉让你熬夜
Sorry for keeping you up.
我认为最好不要等到明天早上
I thought it better not to wait till morning.
哦 没事
Oh, it's no problem.
我是个夜猫子
I'm a night owl.
你觉得我可能得了干燥综合征吗
So you think I might have this sjogren's
-因为我阴道分泌减少吗  -对
- cause of my lack of discharge? - Yeah.
幸好你写在博客上了
It's lucky you wrote about that.
你是否在想  我分享那么多私事
And a little crazy, you're thinking,
有些疯狂
To share that much?
不疯狂
Not crazy.
只是不寻常  你和陌生人如此亲密
Unusual to be so intimate with people you don't know.
但我确实了解他们
But I do know them.
他们读我的博客  我也评论他们的
They read my blog, I comment on theirs.
你没有亲眼见过某人
Just cause you haven't met someone physically
不代表你不了解他
Doesn't mean you don't know them.
你呢  你在谈恋爱吗
What about you? Are you in a relationship?
刚结束
It recently ended.
哦  对不起
Oh. I'm sorry.
平躺下来
Lie flat on your back all the way.
你们之前天天见面是吧
But you saw each other every day, right?
你所想的  有多少告诉了她呢
How much did you tell her about what you were thinking?
还是你们的对话都最后流于
Or did you just end up talking
讨论关于去哪里吃饭
About where you were going to dinner
或是谁去洗衣服之类呢
And who needed to do the laundry?
你和泰勒的关系是如此的吗
Is that what your relationship with Taylor is like?
不是
No.
也许有一点点
Oh, maybe a little.
他真的很好  不过有时候
You know, he's great, but sometimes it's easier
对素不相识的人敞开心扉反而更容易
To open up to people who aren't looking at you.
你需要躺平才能做X光检查
You need to lie flat for us to get the x-ray.
我其实背上不舒服
I'm actually not comfortable on my back.
我们不能这样做吗
Can't we do it this way?
-你扭伤肌肉了吗  -没
- Did you strain a muscle? - No.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我已经为病人安排了心脏手术
I've booked our patient in for heart surgery.
我之前给她做涎管X线
I was doing a sialogram on her,
她不想平躺下
And she didn't want to lie on her back.
这是有心脏瓣膜问题的病人
That's a complaint you hear from people
常见的不适 症状全符合
With heart valve issues. It fits.
干燥综合症损伤了她的心脏
Sjogren's damaged her heart,
引起凝血问题
Causing her clotting problems,
还造成了肾衰竭
Causing her kidneys to fail.
你就凭她不愿躺下的现象
You based all that on the fact
作出了这样的判断吗
That she didn't want to lie down?
不仅如此  在她抱怨不想平躺后
Well, that and the cardiac echo I performed
我还做了心脏超声
After she didn't want to lie down.
二尖瓣几乎没有了
Her mitral valve is nearly gone.
说明她也几乎快死了
Which means she's nearly gone.
天呢  你真的很漂亮
God, you're pretty.
我们可以用猪瓣膜或塑料瓣膜
So we can replace the mitral valve
置换你的二尖瓣
With a pig valve or with a plastic one.
真的从猪身上取吗
From an actual pig?
如果有一天你想要孩子 这是个更好的选择
It's the better choice if you want To have children someday.
用塑料瓣膜你就必须服用抗凝剂
A plastic valve requires you to be on anticoagulants,
它会导致婴儿先天缺陷
Which are known to cause birth defects.
另一方面来说
On the other hand,
猪瓣膜磨损地很快
The pig valve wears out quickly,
十年内  你将需要第二次心脏手术
So you'd need to have heart surgery again in ten years.
我知道你对生孩子还犹豫不决
I know that you're on the fence about having kids,
不过泰勒很想要孩子
But Taylor really wants them.
博客里写着
It's in the blog.
恐怕你们两个需要决定是否要孩子前
I'm afraid you two will need to agree on that decision
达成一致
Earlier than planned.
你决定
It's your call.
能把我的笔记本递给我吗
Can you pass me my laptop?
当真吗
Seriously?
我要看看大家的意见
I want to get some feedback.
你真觉得陌生人不假思索的回答
You really think that asking strangers for some off-the-top- of-their-head response
会有帮助吗
Is gonna be helpful here?
很多你的读者支持保护动物
A lot of your readers are into animal rights.
他们让你差不多成了素食主义者
They've got you 2/3 of the way to vegan.
他们会怎么说
What are they gonna say
要是知道了你花钱用猪的命救自己的命
about you buying your life with the life of a pig?
无论他们说什么  我不是非做不可
Whatever they say, I don't have to do it.
结果不会这样的
It won't work out that way.
我们才是不得不接受这一切的人
And we're the ones that are gonna have to live with this.
求你了  弗兰琪
Please, Frankie.
不要告诉他们
Don't tell them.
要是我开始有所保留
If I start picking and choosing,
我就是不诚实
I'm being dishonest.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thanks.
不过我还是要谢谢
Though I guess I should thank
教会你取悦女性的那个人
Whoever taught you how to please a woman.
或许是林中仙子
Maybe it was the forest nymphs.
把我的迷魂记海报弄回来了
Get my vertigo poster back.
千万别怕  精确找零
Be not afraid. It's exact change.
好
Okay.
你好
Hello?
我期待有关于豪斯的不利消息
I'm looking to get something on House.
你就不能直接找爱情仙子打探秘密吗
Couldn't you just ask the love nymphs for the secret?
不  我的任务是找到豪斯不愿公开的事情
Don't. My mission is to find something that House would not like to see made public
并公诸于众
And make it public.
入伙
In.
不过你比任何人都了解他
But you know him better than anyone.
为什么还要我帮忙
Why do you need my help?
豪斯不会在公寓里留下任何秘密
House would never leave anything secret around the condo.
不过你们和他在一个办公室工作
But you've worked in the same office with him,
断断续续  几年了
On and off, for years.
回想一下
Think back.
过去有没有什么古怪的来电
Were there ever any odd phone calls
或者来访者
Or visitors from the past?
他都明着带妓女来医院
He openly brings prostitutes into the hospital,
他找赌注经纪人下注赌马因为他懒得去马场赌
And he gambles with bookies 'cause he's too lazy to go to the OTB.
你还问
And you're asking for some--
什么  什么
What? What?
什么
What?
他在读《金色情挑》
He's reading the Golden Bowl.
金色  Henry James写的
The gold-- by Henry James?
对
Yeah.
不  不  他不是真的在读
No, no, he's not really reading it.
我不明白
Okay. I don't understand.
那本书少说有400页
That book's at least 400 pages long.
无论他读的什么  只有一半厚
Whatever he's reading is only half that thick.
或许他读的是小字版
Maybe he's reading a version with a smaller font.
他没用老花镜
He's not using his reading glasses.
有道理
That's a good point.
他取下《金色情挑》的封面
He took the cover off the Golden Bowl
放在另一本书的外面  那样就没人知道 他在读什么了
And put it onto this other book so no one would know what he was reading.
无论是什么  他都难以启齿
Whatever it is, he's ashamed of it.
我决定用塑料的
I'm going with plastic.
更合理
It just makes more sense.
我不想以后再做手术了
I don't want another operation later.
你这么做不是因为这个
That's not why you're doing this.
当你第一次告诉我
Look, when you were first telling me
为何你喜欢互联网的时候  你说
About why you love the internet, you said
没人会再感觉孤独了
That no one has to be alone again.
无论是谁  无论你喜欢什么
Whoever you are, whatever you love,
你总能和某人相联系
You can connect with someone.
要是你打算再现波士顿倾茶事件
If you want to recreate the Boston Tea Party
同时打扮成党卫军的样子
While dressed as imperial storm troopers,
你能找到另外10个人
You can find the ten other people in the world
也想这么干
That have always wanted to do that.
现在还是一样
That hasn't changed.
但是你变了
But you have.
你现在做的  已经不是关于联系了
This thing that you do, it's not about connection anymore.
是关于观众
It's about an audience.
是场表演  你时刻关注点击率
It's a performance, and you've got one eye on the number of hits.
你把我们的生活变成了他们的娱乐
You've turned our lives into their entertainment.
你很聪敏
You're smart,
读你的东西很有趣
You're fun to read,
没有问题
It's okay.
不过不要把决定权交给他们
But don't give them this.
要是你说了  不要
Or if you do, don't...
再指望我留在这里
Expect me to be here.
是个不错的掩护
Well, it's a good cover choice.
不是每个人都会看的
It's not like anyone would pick it up.
是卡梅隆最喜欢的书
It's Cameron's favorite book.
我都不知道是说什么的
I don't even know what it's about.
别为难自己
Don't do that to yourself.
这是什么
What the hell?
给他个电脑就像是把钚交给诺博士
Giving him a computer is like giving plutonium to Dr. No.
找到了
Got it.
循序渐进  每日布道
Step by step: sermons for everyday life?
这些是经文布道
These are literal sermons,
牧师写的
Written by a minister.
爱你的邻居即便他们的音响吵得你整夜无眠
Loving thy neighbor even when thy neighbor's stereo is keeping you up at night.
他为何读这个
Why would he read this?
他为何藏着这个
Why would he hide it?
他读圣经  他读古兰经
He reads the bible, he reads the koran,
他说他想知道人们都犯些什么错
He says he likes to know what mistakes people are making.
你觉得他说真诚的吗
You think he's sincere?
你觉得他真能从中悟到什么吗
You think that he's actually getting something out of this?
不知道
I don't know.
真是个伪君子
What a hypocrite.
能怎么利用这事  让他痛苦却还有趣
How can we use this in a cruel yet funny way?
你知道吗
You know what?
别对任何人说
Don't mention this to anyone.
那还有什么意思呢
Well, so what was the point?
我醒的时候  你会在吗
Are you gonna be here when I wake up?
我讨厌你不写博客
I hate that you don't have a blog.
我讨厌我不知道你在想什么
I hate that I don't know what you're thinking.
我们现在不要谈这个
Let's not get into it right now.
我们需要你撑过手术
We need to get you through surgery.
我不想进去  还知道你会陪我度过手术期
I don't want to go in there knowing that you'll stick with me through surgery
只因为这是善良的人该做的
'cause that's what good guys do,
可是一旦我好了  你就会离开
But once I'm better, you'll be gone.
我们不要谈这些
Let's not get into it now.
疼
It hurts.
是她的心脏吗
Is it her heart?
不  在这里
No, it's here.
这里
Here.
把她推进去
Get her inside.
你阑尾破裂
Your appendix burst.
我们不得不摘除
We had to remove it.
活检证实了都是非正常细胞和淋巴癌一致
And the biopsy confirms it was full of abnormal cells consistent with lymphoma.
我得了癌症吗
I have cancer?
我们推迟了心脏瓣膜手术
We've postponed putting in the new valve.
我的意思是  我想我们做 什么  化疗之类的
So I mean, I guess we do, what, chemo and all that stuff?
对  不过显然你患病有段时间了
Yes, but apparently you've had this for some time.
当你盲肠破裂时  就好象水坝坍塌
When your appendix burst, it was like a dam giving way.
癌细胞在你体内循环
The cells went streaming throughout your body.
你们是说会进行治疗  但不认为会有效
So you're saying you'll treat, but you don't expect it to work.
所以不做心脏瓣膜手术了
That's why no valve.
没有意义
It's pointless.
我们医学院院长
Our dean of medicine
已同意一项临床试验
Has approved an experimental treatment.
我们用你独有的癌症细胞标志
We use your unique cancer cell signature
制备针对淋巴癌的疫苗
To create a targeted lymphoma vaccine.
好的  那个能治愈我吗
Okay, so that'll cure me?
我们不确定结果会怎样
Well, we're not actually sure what it'll do,
但目的在于培养你的免疫系统
But the intention is to train your immune system
识别并杀死具有相同恶性标志的细胞
To recognize and kill cells bearing the same malignant signature
同时不伤害健康细胞
While leaving healthy cells alone.
不过  就像福曼医生说的
But, as Dr. Foreman says,
-是试验性的  -我明白
- It's experimental. - I see.
没有这个的话  我们还有多少时间
So without it, what kind of time are we talking about
确切的预期是不可能的
An exact prognosis is impossible.
那么大概呢
Well, how about a guess?
总是有的吧
Something, please.
根据病况和你类似的人的情况...
Based on people in situations like yours...
可能是一年
Maybe a year.
宝贝  该怎么办就怎么办
Baby, whatever we have to do, we'll do.
我会照顾好你
I can take care of you.
我能在家工作
I can work from home.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
谢谢你们让我知道
Thank you for letting me know.
准备好了  我们就可以开始治疗了
We'll start with the treatment whenever it's ready.
她会勇敢地承受化疗  还是毫无反应呢
Is she being a good soldier, or is she in denial?
毫无反应是最常见的第一反应
Denial's not unusual for a first reaction.
或者也可能成为一种病症
Or it could be a symptom.
某些淋巴瘤会影响感知
Some lymphomas affect cognition.
如果是毫无反应  她需要时间适应
If it is denial, she needs time to process.
如果是病症
If it's a symptom,
希望疫苗疗法可以起作用
Hopefully treatment with the vaccine will help.
你好  桑迪
Hey, Sandy.
我能借一下你的车吗
Can I borrow your car?
她给了我钥匙
She gave me the keys.
你是医生  她不过在讨好你
You're a doctor. She was doing you a favor.
她几乎不认识我
She barely knows me.
我曾一度自我欺骗
I've been deluding myself
觉得自己擅长和人交往
That I'm actually connecting with people.
我的初恋  后来被证明
The first person I ever fell in love with
简直就是个演员
Turned out to be a total tool.
我们邂逅时  他幽默  有风度
I mean, he came across all funny and charming
又很有思想  但都是装出来的
And thoughtful, but it was an act.
他要得到一切他想要的东西
He saw something he wanted,
而且他知道他得伪装成什么样子来得到
And he knew he had to behave a certain way to get it.
回头看看  当时我才17  他已经30了
In retrospect, the fact that I was 17 and he was 30
理所当然啊
Should have been a clue.
读懂一个人需要时间
Figuring out who people are takes time.
大概是别人试着让你留下印象的两倍时间
It takes twice as much time if they're trying to impress you.
现在我要么从中领悟  不管谁会借给我车
Now I could take from this that anyone who loans me their car
都别有心机
Has an ulterior motive,
要么我会接受这是学雷锋做好事
Or I can accept that it's just a nice thing to do
但人敬我一尺  我敬人一丈
And take people as they come.
你要打第一针吗
You wanna do the first injection?
你为什么要读牧师写的书
Why are you reading a book by a unitarian minister?
是从读书俱乐部来的
Book club.
-奥普拉(电视主持人)一直说...  -我是认真的
- Oprah was going on and on... - I'm serious.
这  这太扯了
This--this is messed up.
病人写的
Patient wrote it.
不  你没有过叫这名字的病人
No, you've never treated a patient with this name.
我查过了
I looked it up.
是我的心理医生留给我的作业
It's an assignment from my therapist.
不  不是的
No, it wasn't.
你尊敬的人是不会期待给你这种东西来帮助你的
No one you respect would give you this and expect it to be helpful.
不过是本书罢了
It's a book!
关于布道的
Of sermons.
对别人来说  是灵魂的启蒙
For anyone else, spiritually enlightening.
对你来说  简直就是脑袋里进水
For you, it's practically a psychotic break.
我知道有时候不用维可丁
I know that you have trouble sometimes with the pain
你的腿疼会给你造成困扰  是因为这个吗
Without the vicodin-- is that it?
难道你已经别无选择
Are you so out of options,
要靠那些你认为毫无理性的东西来寻求答案吗
You're looking for answers in what you consider irrationality?
我没事  相信我
I'm all right. Trust me.
没事是因为你又吃维可丁了吗
Are you all right because you're back on vicodin?
我说过了  相信我
I said, "Trust me."
我知道这其中有所意义
I know this means something.
介意还给我吗
Do you mind?
我还没看完
I haven't finished it yet.
多谢你的礼物
Thanks for the gifts
但如果这些故事能让你安度
But if these stories have helped you
灵魂上的不安...
Through some spiritual turmoil--
看看第六章
Read chapter six,
名字是  "闭嘴"
Entitled "Shut the hell up."
我倒很欣赏这章  药物治疗前
I appreciated the inscription about the benefits of prayer
祈祷的好处
Before medical treatments.
而且我认为
And I think it's great
你能成为上帝的证人  真好
That you have been called to witness by the lord.
第二章  "去死"
Chapter two, "Bite me."
13正要给我们的病人
Thirteen's giving our patient
注射她的第三针疫苗
Her third vaccine injection.
目前为止  她反应良好
She's responding well so far.
你们从哪来的这些书
Where'd you get all these copies?
书已经卖完了啊
It's out of print.
我给作者打过电话
I called the author.
他地下室里有好几箱呢
He's got cartons of the thing in his basement.
你打电话给他了吗  你说了什么
You called him? What'd you say?
我认识的某人从这本书里得到了
That I knew some people who could benefit spiritually
-灵魂上的升华  -你提到我了吗
- From the book. - Did you mention me?
没有
Mm, no.
高烧华氏104度
Fever's at 104.
抗体破坏了她的自身免疫反应系统
The antibodies tripped her autoimmune response.
疫苗正在害死她
The vaccine is killing her.
很显然不起作用
Well, clearly it's not working.
必须停止疫苗治疗
You have to stop the vaccine.
没错  放弃治疗吧  让她按计划去死吧
Sure. Give up. Let her die on schedule.
总比在死的更快要好一些
It's better than speeding up the schedule.
这种症状来的有多快
How quickly did this come on?
今天下午我叫醒她
She was all right when I woke her this afternoon
准备打第二针疫苗时还好好的
To give her the second injection.
是因为应激
Of the stimulating agent,
加上第一针疫苗
Which, added to the first injection,
让她的免疫系统负担过重
Switched her immune reaction into overdrive.
她怎么会睡着呢
Why was she sleeping?
有谁能在白天的医院里睡着呢
Who can sleep in a hospital during the daytime?
我一点也不惊讶  她很累
I'm not surprised. She's tired.
她一直是个夜猫子
She's always been a night owl.
在治疗她的过程中
Just by treating her,
我们完全颠倒了她的生物钟
We've completely disrupted her schedule.
她博客上是这么说的吗
Is that what her blog says?
她是个夜猫子吗
She's a night owl?
不  是她告诉我的
No, she told me.
什么时候  现在  曾经
In what tense? Is? Was?
还是将来呢
Will have been?
我不清楚
I'm not sure.
你在看什么
What are you onto?
看看这个帖子上的时间
Look at the time stamp on this post.
凌晨2点半
2:30 a.M.
这张是凌晨4点
Here's one at 4:00 a.M.
不管他在看什么  都改变不了事实
Whatever he's onto doesn't change the fact
她有淋巴瘤  而我们给她用了危险的疫苗
That she has lymphoma and we gave her a dangerous vaccine.
-我们需要...  -看看6个月以前
- We need to-- - six months ago,
她还是白天写帖子的
She's posting in the daytime.
2年前  也是白天
Two years ago, daytime.
那是她的自然生物钟
That's her natural rhythm.
黑白颠倒
Day-night reversal.
难道不是肝病的症状吗
Sign of liver disease?
那些不像是淋巴瘤的病症
Which doesn't fit lymphoma.
但我们知道她已经有淋巴瘤了
But we know she has lymphoma.
我们知道她有看起来像是
We know she has the cell atypia
淋巴瘤的异常细胞
That indicates lymphoma.
给她的肝脏做活检
Biopsy her liver.
我刚才说的很酷  不是吗
That was pretty cool what I did, right?
你想弄明白吗
You wanna make out?
你没有得淋巴瘤
You don't have lymphoma.
但你说过我的阑尾上都是癌症细胞
But you said my appendix was full of cancer cells.
你阑尾上确实满是看起来像是淋巴瘤的异常细胞
Your appendix was full of cells that showed a lymphocytic atypia.
我们现在认为那是由于某些
We now think they were a granulomatous buildup
不明原因产生的肉芽肿增生
From some unknown cause.
那就是说...
So...
我不会死了吗
I'm not dying?
实际上  你比我们想象的要死的快
You're actually dying more quickly than we thought.
除非我们弄清楚
Unless we figure out
是什么导致了你的肝脏衰竭...
What's causing your liver failure...
你还有3到4天时间
You have three or four days.
你们说我还有3到4天是什么意思
What the hell do you mean I have three or four days?
看来我们跳过毫无反应这关了
Well, we're past denial.
可能不是我们造成她发烧的
Maybe we didn't cause the fever.
我们给她用了疫苗
We gave her the vaccine,
而她开始发烧
And her fever spiked.
-我看来是...  -是的  但停用
- Seems to me...  - Yes, but it persisted
疫苗之后她还在发烧
After we took her off the vaccine.
假如是一种新的病症呢
What if it's a new symptom?
好的
Okay.
所以  发烧加上异常细胞  凝血障碍
So we add fever to cell atypia, coagulopathy,
肾脏  心脏  肝脏...
Kidney, heart, liver...
应该是一种传染病
It has to be an infection.
但是是什么传染病呢  她认识的人没人得病
But which one? No one she knows is sick.
她也没有出去旅游
She hasn't traveled anywhere.
在她给我们的病史里没有任何发现
There's nothing in the history she gave us.
在她的博客里也一无所获
Nothing in her blog.
感染源肯定很特殊
There has to be something unique to this infection.
它的传播以及呈现方式也很特殊
Something about its transmission and the way it manifests.
她肯定遗漏了一些信息
There has to be something she's not telling us.
没有
There isn't.
她把所有一切都告诉了大家
She's told us, and everyone else, everything.
给她用广谱抗生素
Start her on broad-spectrum antibiotics.
既然我们都知晓一切
Since we know everything,
我们就该治疗一切
we might as well treat for everything.
我随手拿了一本奇斯放在休息室里的书
I picked up one of the copies of the book that Chase left in the lounge.
如果你继续这样
If you're gonna be this way,
我不会邀请你参加我的洗礼
I'm not gonna invite you to my baptism.
这还是我第一次看见真的书封皮
First time I'd seen the real dust jacket.
后面是作者的照片
The inside back flap, there was a picture of the author.
当我认出相片的人物时我无比惊讶
Imagine how surprised I was when I recognized him.
你的生父是一名牧师吗
Your biological father is a minister?
自然选择规律不总是万无一失的
Natural selection is not an infallible force.
我不明白
I don't get it.
他是你们家一名朋友
I mean, okay, he was a friend of the family.
你只有在小时候见过他
You'd only known him when you were a kid.
可如果你现在想见他
But if you wanted to meet him now,
想知道他现在的容貌
Get an idea of what he's like,
为什么不直接去找他呢
Why not just go talk to him?
你好  我叫格雷戈  你曾睡了我母亲
"Hi, it's Greg. You slept with my mother."
这种事情你做得出来
You're capable of it.
我只是稍微有些好奇
I was mildly curious.
但仅能驱使我去阅读他的著作 还不足以驱使我去给他打电话
Enough to read a book, not enough to make a phone call.
不是吧  你不仅仅看这本书
Please. You didn't read this.
你深入研究了它  为什么
You studied it. Why?
你这辈子都认为这上面说的都是废话
All your life, you've thought this was crap.
你不可能突然之间改变
You can't suddenly turn around
在一堆废话上建立一个新的世界观
and build a whole new worldview based on crap.
废话
Crap.
你最好不是为了逃避这严肃对话而装的
You better not be faking this just to get out of a tough conversation.
你排便的吧
Do you poop?
别害羞
Come on.
每个人都排便
Everybody poops.
我上学的时候看过一本书
I read the book in medical school.
-漂浮还是下沉  -他就是那个怪才
- Sinkers or floaters? - This is the wizard.
软便带油花
Greasy and soft
还是干硬颗粒状
or hard and pellet-like?
漂浮  软便带有油膜
Floaters and the first one.
你不得不说谎
You just had to be so swoft.
你是个伪君子
You're a hypocrite.
虽然你不撒谎  没有秘密
No lies, no secrets,
不过你所有的秘密都停滞于你的结肠里
but everything stops at your colon.
你写了4000页的博客 却对你的粪便只字未提
4,000 pages, not one word about BMs
想必你也不会去闻它
And I bet yours don't smell at all.
没人愿意听这些吧
Nobody wants to hear about that stuff.
读者们是不关心
Readers don't.
不真心关心你的人们也不会在意这事
People who don't really care about you don't.
但是医生在意
But doctors might.
那些黏糊糊的东西数个月前变样了  是吗
The icky stuff changed, right, a few months ago?
那是因为我吃素了
Well, I became a vegetarian.
大多数人都误会素食主义者的饮食规律
A lot of people misunderstand how a vegetarian diet works.
你摄入的食物越精细
You take in less unusable material,
消化吸收效率就越高
and your waste gets more efficient.
大便越容易干结
Harder and rounder.
看看兔子的粪便就知道了
Just look at the feces of rabbits.
说真的  我好像有些
Seriously. I think I might have some.
吸收不良
Malabsorption.
她的身体无法吸收必要的营养
Her system's not retaining the necessary nutrients.
肠胃感染导致吸收不良
A g.I. Infection causes malabsorption,
肉芽肿筑成细胞
Granulomatous buildup of cells.
应该不是传染病  因为她周围没人得病
It's not contagious since no one around her got sick--
-惠普尔病  -惠普尔病（肠源性脂肪代谢障碍）
- Whipple's disease. - Whipple's disease.
一人一块骨头
Let's split the credit.
给她用复方磺胺甲基异恶唑
Start her on co-trimoxazole.
每个人都需要有些秘密
We all need some secrets.
只要不毒害我们 这些秘密会给予我们温暖与保护
As long as they don't kill us, they keep us safe and warm.
我...
I'm...
我就要没事了吗
I'm gonna be okay?
你还是要移植新的心脏瓣膜
You'll still need a new heart valve,
而且你还需要服用几年的药
and you'll be on meds for a few years,
不过基本上  是的
But, basically, yeah.
你的病会好的
Your odds are good.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
看来我以后得用猪心瓣膜
I think I wanna go with the pig valve.
想必你要是不与大家分享这个消息你会抓狂的
I know you'll go crazy if you don't tell people.
你真贴心
Thank god you're an enabler.
你觉得在网上聊天比面对面
Do you think people can actually know each other better
更容易了解对方吗
on the internet than face-to-face?
外貌会影响人的判断力
Faces can be distracting,
不过通过一个人的眼睛 能了解更多
But there's nothing better than looking into someone's eyes
以及诸如此类的问题
and, well, everything that goes with that.
我不明白
I don't know.
人们见面后  他们以貌取人
People meet, they like something superficial,
然后他们想当然的去揣测对方的性格
and then they fill in the blanks with whatever they want to believe.
为什么你为此而苦恼
Why are you so hung up on this?
我绝不相信仅仅是因为 你刚察觉自己长的帅吧
I refuse to believe it's all because you just noticed you have a nice face.
你刚结束了一段感情
You just came off a relationship.
你觉得事情更深层次
You know things go deeper than...
就是因为这些吗
Is that what this is about?
你和卡梅隆
You and Cameron?
起初是我先追她的
I was the one that pursued her.
或许我是有些想当然
Maybe I was just filling in the blanks.
也许...
Maybe...
或许我的第一感是正确的
Maybe the first reaction was right.
我们只是互相接近的两个人
We were just two people who were in proximity
然后发现被彼此吸引了  我不该...
And found each other attractive, and I never should have...
妄想症
Paranoia.
你对她是有感觉的
You felt something real.
她也如此
So did she.
别想否认这一切
Don't try to take it back now.
能把车借给我吗
Can I borrow your car?
不借
No.
你为什么可以看你爸写的书
Why would it make more sense for you to read your father's book
而不愿意和他说话呢
than to go talk with him?
你会写书吗
Can you write a book?
那我就不用跟你说话了
So I can stop talking to you?
你不是在寻求精神洗礼
You weren't looking for some big catharsis.
你不愿意靠近他
You didn't want to hug the guy.
你只是想知道他的思维
You just wanted to know how his head works.
他的想法
How he thinks.
我只是沉迷于牧师们的思考方式
'cause I'm fascinated with how ministers think.
你不是泛泛之辈  豪斯
Because you're not ordinary, House
你属于边缘群体
You're way out there on the fringe somewhere.
我是你最好的朋友
I'm your best friend,
可有一半时间  我都无法理解你的行为
and half the time, I don't understand you.
你是孤独的
You're alone.
你会孤独终老
Been alone your whole life.
当你看那本书的时候
When you read that book,
你希望在那套有神论的下面
you were hoping that somewhere, underneath all that talk of god,
找到一种你所熟悉的
there would be a way of thinking,
思维方式
a mind that you could recognize.
你想要的跟我们一样
You wanted what we all want.
詹超人变形成水形态的能力吗[漫画Wonder Twin]
The power to transform into any water-based object?
你希望俯瞰世界能够发现一些你的同类人
To look across the gulf and know there's someone else like you.
你至少得告诉我你有没有什么发现呢
At least tell me this-- did you find something there?
神论那些事情的背后
Underneath the god stuff...
更多的关于神的事情
more god stuff.
帮我把那个拿下
Get me an * to take that down